1
00:00:08,130 --> 00:00:09,920
Previously on "Billions"...

2
00:00:09,920 --> 00:00:12,130
And you've been with him longer than you've been with me.

3
00:00:12,130 --> 00:00:13,170
You and Axe.

4
00:00:13,170 --> 00:00:14,320
And it's deep,

5
00:00:14,390 --> 00:00:17,160
and I fucking hate it.

6
00:00:17,380 --> 00:00:19,420
I've got a source, an janitor.

7
00:00:19,670 --> 00:00:22,010
That's as high as I can nail down so far,

8
00:00:22,020 --> 00:00:23,270
but he's already coming through.

9
00:00:23,270 --> 00:00:25,460
I'm gonna get you back from Eastern and make you happy.

10
00:00:25,460 --> 00:00:26,760
I'd like to be happy.

11
00:00:26,890 --> 00:00:30,400
Got this made 'cause I was so fucking proud of Chuck

12
00:00:30,400 --> 00:00:31,670
for pushing back.

13
00:00:32,370 --> 00:00:34,050
You know I didn't drive all the way up here to Westport

14
00:00:34,060 --> 00:00:35,700
to give out "Attaboys."

15
00:00:35,740 --> 00:00:38,730
Had to bring the kick ass... with love.

16
00:00:38,880 --> 00:00:40,610
Bad day. Something happened.

17
00:00:40,620 --> 00:00:42,490
- But I'll fix it. - Wendy?

18
00:00:43,090 --> 00:00:44,350
You can't trust her.

19
00:00:44,350 --> 00:00:45,560
I need an adjustment.

20
00:00:45,560 --> 00:00:47,390
You're finally ready for a real session.

21
00:00:47,390 --> 00:00:48,720
I take care of my people...

22
00:00:48,720 --> 00:00:51,410
same as when Mick Danzig gets tackled on his lawn

23
00:00:51,410 --> 00:00:53,360
with a machine gun in his fucking hands.

24
00:00:53,790 --> 00:00:55,420
I'm the one who pays off the cops

25
00:00:55,420 --> 00:00:58,650
to make the problem go away. That's what I do here.

26
00:00:58,650 --> 00:01:00,900
Took me apart, put me together again.

27
00:01:08,750 --> 00:01:09,610
Mm. Red!

28
00:01:09,610 --> 00:01:11,440
You didn't get permission from Wendy?

29
00:01:12,150 --> 00:01:13,650
She's intractable.

30
00:01:40,830 --> 00:01:45,840
m

31
00:01:40,830 --> 00:01:45,840
m

32
00:01:40,830 --> 00:01:45,840
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

33
00:01:40,830 --> 00:01:45,840
m 330

34
00:01:45,840 --> 00:02:15,840
m 195 

35
00:01:45,840 --> 00:02:15,840
m 20 

36
00:01:45,840 --> 00:02:15,840
m 71 

37
00:02:04,270 --> 00:02:07,110
I woke your assistant and made her tell me where you were.

38
00:02:07,890 --> 00:02:09,410
I need to have her fired.

39
00:02:09,930 --> 00:02:11,970
That's what I'd do, but you're nicer than me.

40
00:02:12,480 --> 00:02:13,440
That I am.

41
00:02:14,660 --> 00:02:17,110
Our comp meeting will happen as scheduled.

42
00:02:18,240 --> 00:02:19,330
Your bonus will reflect

43
00:02:19,330 --> 00:02:22,360
your overall contribution to the firm, as always.

44
00:02:23,310 --> 00:02:25,560
But I needed to do something else for you...

45
00:02:26,720 --> 00:02:28,490
...after what you did for me the other night.

46
00:02:29,830 --> 00:02:31,180
Something special.

47
00:02:31,930 --> 00:02:33,730
- That's for you. - Axe.

48
00:02:40,720 --> 00:02:42,900
This is un-fucking-believable.

49
00:02:43,630 --> 00:02:44,730
Thank you.

50
00:02:46,400 --> 00:02:48,070
This time, thank you.

51
00:02:53,390 --> 00:02:56,010
Okay. I gotta go.

52
00:02:56,330 --> 00:02:58,060
I'm on my way to meet Wags.

53
00:02:58,140 --> 00:02:59,800
Starting a capital raise.

54
00:03:01,190 --> 00:03:02,500
After our session,

55
00:03:03,050 --> 00:03:05,140
I had the sudden clarity that we were ready,

56
00:03:06,260 --> 00:03:07,330
that I was ready.

57
00:03:08,380 --> 00:03:09,340
Go get 'em.

58
00:03:10,830 --> 00:03:11,700
I will.

59
00:03:16,570 --> 00:03:17,530
I see it...

60
00:03:19,210 --> 00:03:20,790
...looking at you, that you're ready.

61
00:03:21,560 --> 00:03:24,340
But they may not be. At least...not yet.

62
00:03:45,480 --> 00:03:46,600
Good to see you, man.

63
00:03:52,220 --> 00:03:53,630
Welcome back, Lonnie.

64
00:03:54,190 --> 00:03:55,550
Can't thank you enough.

65
00:03:57,710 --> 00:03:59,070
- Please. - Excellent.

66
00:04:05,230 --> 00:04:06,080
Don't even unpack.

67
00:04:06,090 --> 00:04:08,580
I've got an assignment that has to happen now.

68
00:04:08,630 --> 00:04:09,550
I'm listening.

69
00:04:10,030 --> 00:04:12,400
There's a tip that I need you to bird dog for me.

70
00:04:12,400 --> 00:04:14,090
Well, I'm birdy as a springer spaniel.

71
00:04:14,090 --> 00:04:15,030
What is it?

72
00:04:15,550 --> 00:04:18,990
Criminal behavior perpetrated by Bobby Axelrod.

73
00:04:18,990 --> 00:04:20,670
I thought the office got that case pulled.

74
00:04:20,670 --> 00:04:21,830
Well, this case would be different.

75
00:04:21,830 --> 00:04:25,110
It's not white collar, federal firearms.

76
00:04:26,210 --> 00:04:27,210
Bribery.

77
00:04:28,230 --> 00:04:29,020
That's a monster.

78
00:04:29,020 --> 00:04:31,060
Yeah. It can't be tied to me.

79
00:04:34,000 --> 00:04:35,360
Start in Greenwich.

80
00:04:35,940 --> 00:04:37,670
Mick Danzig.

81
00:04:37,690 --> 00:04:40,200
D-a-n-z-i-g.

82
00:04:40,200 --> 00:04:41,670
Now you loop Connerty and his team in

83
00:04:41,670 --> 00:04:44,240
when the time is right, but again...

84
00:04:44,730 --> 00:04:46,550
...leave me out of it, Lonnie.

85
00:04:46,550 --> 00:04:48,150
Yeah. I'll jump right in,

86
00:04:48,160 --> 00:04:50,380
keep your involvement entre nous.

87
00:04:51,020 --> 00:04:51,980
Very good.

88
00:04:53,940 --> 00:04:55,820
Why do I have to carry this shit?

89
00:04:55,820 --> 00:04:58,570
I'm not gonna carry it. You know the drill.

90
00:04:58,850 --> 00:05:00,430
Principal comes in unburdened,

91
00:05:00,430 --> 00:05:02,170
free but for his brilliant ideas.

92
00:05:02,170 --> 00:05:03,210
And the COO -- he lugs the books

93
00:05:03,210 --> 00:05:04,830
like a schoolboy with a crush.

94
00:05:04,830 --> 00:05:06,640
There's no reason to even have these books.

95
00:05:06,640 --> 00:05:08,670
This info can fit on the flash drive.

96
00:05:09,090 --> 00:05:10,510
Do you know why we wear ties?

97
00:05:10,600 --> 00:05:12,610
To signify seriousness of purpose.

98
00:05:12,620 --> 00:05:15,190
Ours is not to question why, ...but to do, if...

99
00:05:15,190 --> 00:05:17,600
...like the schoolboy, we want our kiss.

100
00:05:20,130 --> 00:05:22,400
Roller coasters are great at an amusement park.

101
00:05:22,400 --> 00:05:23,510
I love 'em.

102
00:05:23,930 --> 00:05:25,910
The ups and downs are what make it worth riding.

103
00:05:25,910 --> 00:05:27,490
Not so much in an investment vehicle.

104
00:05:27,490 --> 00:05:30,820
Unlike a roller coaster, our returns only go up.

105
00:05:34,560 --> 00:05:38,700
But your life, Axe... The fund's profile.

106
00:05:38,810 --> 00:05:41,740
You went from managing 10 billion in outside money to half that.

107
00:05:41,760 --> 00:05:43,800
- All of it yours. - That's true.

108
00:05:44,280 --> 00:05:46,500
A year like that makes you question everything.

109
00:05:46,830 --> 00:05:48,570
Makes you find new answers, too.

110
00:05:48,930 --> 00:05:49,960
What'd you figure out?

111
00:05:50,650 --> 00:05:52,200
That it's all about my why.

112
00:05:54,160 --> 00:05:57,390
I don't get to think about business in such an esoteric manner.

113
00:05:57,890 --> 00:06:00,720
I have to evaluate risk, reward, return. That's it.

114
00:06:01,330 --> 00:06:02,770
And to that end...

115
00:06:03,430 --> 00:06:04,580
my people have a few questions.

116
00:06:04,580 --> 00:06:06,450
Your Sharpe Ratio's very low.

117
00:06:06,450 --> 00:06:09,110
How does an idea turn into an investment at your shop?

118
00:06:09,110 --> 00:06:11,330
What's your mosaic theory at Axe Capital?

119
00:06:11,570 --> 00:06:13,320
Fees from funds like ours

120
00:06:13,330 --> 00:06:14,780
used to pay your overhead.

121
00:06:15,410 --> 00:06:18,410
How are you dealing with floating it all yourself?

122
00:06:19,640 --> 00:06:21,740
I can't allow myself to care about that.

123
00:06:22,820 --> 00:06:24,230
What I do care about

124
00:06:24,760 --> 00:06:27,710
is making decisions to benefit a greater number of people.

125
00:06:28,790 --> 00:06:31,150
Now when I'm only working for myself or my staff,

126
00:06:31,370 --> 00:06:32,550
I'm sharp enough.

127
00:06:33,800 --> 00:06:36,660
But when I'm making decisions for you as well as me,

128
00:06:37,080 --> 00:06:39,720
that's when I'm twice as careful, twice as focused,

129
00:06:39,720 --> 00:06:43,360
because I cannot live with losing somebody else's money.

130
00:06:44,090 --> 00:06:45,380
That's my why.

131
00:06:46,080 --> 00:06:47,630
Have you had your Carter Staley meeting yet?

132
00:06:47,640 --> 00:06:48,950
Is he allocating to you?

133
00:06:50,920 --> 00:06:51,950
He's a lemming.

134
00:06:52,540 --> 00:06:54,590
Soon as you net one major allocator, he'll be in.

135
00:06:54,590 --> 00:06:56,330
He was supposed to be the major allocator

136
00:06:56,330 --> 00:06:57,640
that would make the others comfortable.

137
00:06:57,640 --> 00:06:59,170
We just need one domino.

138
00:07:01,400 --> 00:07:02,850
Yeah. Greenwich PD.

139
00:07:05,490 --> 00:07:07,140
Thank you for bringing that in, Robin.

140
00:07:07,140 --> 00:07:08,240
My pleasure, sir.

141
00:07:08,350 --> 00:07:10,110
Duty rosters for the last several months,

142
00:07:10,110 --> 00:07:13,280
along with vacations times and radio call log.

143
00:07:14,020 --> 00:07:15,150
If your subpoenas are in order,

144
00:07:15,150 --> 00:07:16,940
would you mind telling me what you're looking for?

145
00:07:17,100 --> 00:07:17,950
Yes.

146
00:07:19,900 --> 00:07:21,180
Yes, I mind telling you.

147
00:07:23,460 --> 00:07:25,910
So you are that confident you can get back

148
00:07:25,910 --> 00:07:27,390
to the numbers you were at.

149
00:07:27,390 --> 00:07:29,990
No doubt. I have meetings lined up all week.

150
00:07:29,990 --> 00:07:30,950
Terrific.

151
00:07:31,340 --> 00:07:33,440
- Is Staley aboard yet? - Not yet.

152
00:07:34,310 --> 00:07:35,330
Doesn't matter.

153
00:07:35,650 --> 00:07:37,370
I'd be thrilled to be first money in.

154
00:07:37,450 --> 00:07:38,590
Wunderbar.

155
00:07:41,740 --> 00:07:43,460
- Another whiff. - Yep.

156
00:07:44,100 --> 00:07:46,090
If it's that's easy, you know they're not coming in.

157
00:07:46,090 --> 00:07:48,270
Nope. Just there for the story.

158
00:07:48,270 --> 00:07:50,680
"Axe pitched me. How the mighty have fallen."

159
00:07:51,680 --> 00:07:53,520
We gotta close Carter Staley.

160
00:08:02,390 --> 00:08:04,800
Officer Salter responded to a disturbance call

161
00:08:04,800 --> 00:08:06,230
at the Danzig residence

162
00:08:06,230 --> 00:08:09,180
but found no reason to pursue matters with Mr. Danzig.

163
00:08:09,180 --> 00:08:11,190
My client has nothing further to say.

164
00:08:11,650 --> 00:08:13,190
We're going to be interviewing the rest of the shift

165
00:08:13,200 --> 00:08:14,530
that was on that night.

166
00:08:14,650 --> 00:08:16,530
I'm gonna make it very clear to them.

167
00:08:16,530 --> 00:08:19,080
Cooperation results in candy canes.

168
00:08:19,080 --> 00:08:20,950
Obfuscation will get you coal.

169
00:08:20,950 --> 00:08:23,630
Now let's talk about this vacation

170
00:08:23,630 --> 00:08:26,560
your client took to Vanuatu in early September.

171
00:08:26,650 --> 00:08:28,340
- What was the purpose -- - Recreation.

172
00:08:29,030 --> 00:08:30,740
If you want to lodge formal charges,

173
00:08:30,740 --> 00:08:32,350
let's rock and roll. Otherwise, you --

174
00:08:32,350 --> 00:08:35,760
Don't you worry. We're about to rock like Cameo in '86.

175
00:08:38,940 --> 00:08:41,160
You're smashing back every one of their questions

176
00:08:41,170 --> 00:08:42,550
...when they fucking ask them.

177
00:08:42,720 --> 00:08:44,070
Like Agassi in his prime.

178
00:08:44,070 --> 00:08:45,080
The dam is gonna break soon.

179
00:08:45,080 --> 00:08:46,920
I don't need the Coach K bullshit right now.

180
00:08:46,920 --> 00:08:48,170
Well, what do you need?

181
00:08:49,050 --> 00:08:50,460
Not sure. Something.

182
00:08:58,760 --> 00:09:00,100
Throw those books aside.

183
00:09:00,530 --> 00:09:03,550
No, take those books, go back to the office,

184
00:09:03,550 --> 00:09:04,880
and I'll see you after.

185
00:09:22,830 --> 00:09:24,170
Here's how simple it is.

186
00:09:25,150 --> 00:09:30,070
I've outperformed the S&P by 38.7% over the past 15 years.

187
00:09:30,610 --> 00:09:32,330
But that's not at issue here.

188
00:09:33,350 --> 00:09:36,800
The issue is the turmoil,

189
00:09:37,360 --> 00:09:41,130
the aspersions cast on my fund and me.

190
00:09:41,590 --> 00:09:43,180
I'm talking about 9/11,

191
00:09:43,730 --> 00:09:44,740
arrests,

192
00:09:45,560 --> 00:09:47,420
whether I run a clean shop.

193
00:09:48,290 --> 00:09:49,490
And I understand that.

194
00:09:50,700 --> 00:09:51,890
In your shoes,

195
00:09:53,330 --> 00:09:54,790
I'd factor it in, too.

196
00:09:55,080 --> 00:09:58,880
But I'd also factor in the true cost of missed opportunity.

197
00:10:01,210 --> 00:10:03,740
In the span of...say, what? A year?

198
00:10:03,850 --> 00:10:05,970
Nobody's gonna give a shit about any of that.

199
00:10:07,160 --> 00:10:09,530
But the growth that you will have missed out on?

200
00:10:09,770 --> 00:10:11,850
That's gonna eat you from the inside.

201
00:10:12,010 --> 00:10:15,080
In a year's time, I'd be happy to revisit.

202
00:10:15,080 --> 00:10:15,710
In a year's time,

203
00:10:15,720 --> 00:10:17,550
you're not gonna be able to get me on the phone.

204
00:10:18,500 --> 00:10:20,220
When I walk out that door today,

205
00:10:20,700 --> 00:10:22,210
we are friends for life,

206
00:10:22,940 --> 00:10:26,010
or you don't exist to me ever again.

207
00:10:29,310 --> 00:10:31,620
I'm about to go on the run of a lifetime.

208
00:10:32,280 --> 00:10:34,800
I am aligned. I feel it.

209
00:10:35,230 --> 00:10:37,150
And I know you can see it.

210
00:10:37,470 --> 00:10:40,650
I'm here, but in ten seconds,

211
00:10:40,650 --> 00:10:42,560
the bullet train leaves.

212
00:10:44,820 --> 00:10:46,470
And if you wanna make money,

213
00:10:47,870 --> 00:10:49,450
climb the fuck aboard.

214
00:10:50,140 --> 00:10:51,330
Yes!

215
00:10:54,700 --> 00:10:56,550
I shouted out when you called me.

216
00:10:56,560 --> 00:10:58,180
Holy fuck, we're back!

217
00:10:58,200 --> 00:10:59,180
Great, boss.

218
00:10:59,930 --> 00:11:01,430
Come on. Come on!

219
00:11:01,770 --> 00:11:03,690
Can't imagine how the bonus comp sessions would've gone

220
00:11:03,690 --> 00:11:04,870
if it went the other way.

221
00:11:04,880 --> 00:11:06,060
- Welcome back. - Good to see you.

222
00:11:06,060 --> 00:11:07,300
Good to see you, man.

223
00:11:07,850 --> 00:11:09,750
So... wanted to hit the ground running,

224
00:11:09,760 --> 00:11:12,400
but wanted you guys looped in on what I'm working

225
00:11:12,400 --> 00:11:13,170
-- Axelrod.

226
00:11:13,170 --> 00:11:15,690
Mandate to find extracurricular crimes.

227
00:11:16,350 --> 00:11:17,370
You found one?

228
00:11:17,380 --> 00:11:19,140
Bribery of police officials.

229
00:11:20,510 --> 00:11:22,710
Yeah, I got a pair of, uh, Greenwich cops

230
00:11:22,710 --> 00:11:25,040
with links to an Axelrod PM taking a vacation

231
00:11:25,040 --> 00:11:26,610
to Vanuatu a little while back.

232
00:11:26,610 --> 00:11:28,800
Yeah, you know who vacations there? No one.

233
00:11:28,800 --> 00:11:31,760
Oh, that place is a haven for offshore banking.

234
00:11:31,940 --> 00:11:34,930
Wait, you think these cops went to visit their payoff money?

235
00:11:35,240 --> 00:11:36,540
Set up their accounts?

236
00:11:36,570 --> 00:11:38,180
Yeah, I had 'em turn their heads and cough,

237
00:11:38,180 --> 00:11:39,370
and they didn't give anything up,

238
00:11:39,370 --> 00:11:41,950
but... once the money's been tracked,

239
00:11:42,000 --> 00:11:43,250
they won't have a choice.

240
00:11:43,640 --> 00:11:45,060
I'll e-mail you guys what I have.

241
00:11:45,060 --> 00:11:46,410
- This could really be something. - Yeah.

242
00:11:46,410 --> 00:11:48,490
- How'd you step into it? - On a hunch.

243
00:11:48,490 --> 00:11:50,370
I reviewed arrest records of all Axe Capital --

244
00:11:50,370 --> 00:11:52,090
There were no arrests. We checked.

245
00:11:52,090 --> 00:11:55,410
Right. So then I looked into the suspicious activity reports

246
00:11:55,410 --> 00:11:57,720
in the Greenwich PD's dispatch log.

247
00:11:57,720 --> 00:11:59,820
Found a few that raised a red flag that hadn't gone

248
00:11:59,820 --> 00:12:01,080
all the way through the system.

249
00:12:03,080 --> 00:12:04,600
That's some fucking hunch.

250
00:12:42,680 --> 00:12:44,810
Don't hand me that card. I gave you that card.

251
00:12:45,630 --> 00:12:46,550
Raul.

252
00:12:48,090 --> 00:12:49,860
Okay, you went this far, get right to it.

253
00:12:50,000 --> 00:12:51,340
You have a problem.

254
00:12:52,510 --> 00:12:54,360
You greased some fellows in my union.

255
00:12:54,570 --> 00:12:55,510
If you say I did.

256
00:12:55,510 --> 00:12:56,450
I do.

257
00:12:57,300 --> 00:12:58,320
And it worked.

258
00:12:59,480 --> 00:13:02,450
Word is the US Attorney's office knows something about

259
00:13:03,080 --> 00:13:05,890
an...automatic weapon, paid off cops,

260
00:13:06,040 --> 00:13:07,320
and one of your guys.

261
00:13:07,320 --> 00:13:08,500
You wouldn't know anything about it, would you?

262
00:13:08,500 --> 00:13:10,370
I think I had a dream about it once.

263
00:13:10,480 --> 00:13:12,010
Further word says they're rolling through people,

264
00:13:12,010 --> 00:13:15,280
rolling over them to get to the truth of the story.

265
00:13:16,460 --> 00:13:17,510
How'd it get to you?

266
00:13:17,510 --> 00:13:19,630
I make it my business to still know what's going on.

267
00:13:19,800 --> 00:13:22,160
I have three sons and six nephews in various branches,

268
00:13:22,170 --> 00:13:23,260
and we don't miss much.

269
00:13:23,260 --> 00:13:24,450
That's for sure.

270
00:13:29,790 --> 00:13:31,880
I'll say a more complete thank you at a later date,

271
00:13:31,880 --> 00:13:35,970
but...thank you for being a friend.

272
00:13:35,970 --> 00:13:36,810
Always.

273
00:13:37,660 --> 00:13:40,260
And slow down on these goddamn winding roads,

274
00:13:40,800 --> 00:13:43,190
or next time it won't be the US Attorney that gets you.

275
00:13:58,230 --> 00:13:59,970
If one of the officers flips,

276
00:14:00,400 --> 00:14:02,960
confesses, or if they find the money or gun

277
00:14:02,970 --> 00:14:04,210
and can trace it...

278
00:14:04,310 --> 00:14:07,500
They cannot trace the funds back to us. Yet.

279
00:14:08,160 --> 00:14:09,280
They were securely handled,

280
00:14:09,290 --> 00:14:12,210
intermediaries, overseas banks.

281
00:14:12,530 --> 00:14:15,120
But eventually, everything has a trail.

282
00:14:15,350 --> 00:14:17,290
The laws regarding this type of thing --

283
00:14:17,730 --> 00:14:19,440
bribery of public officials,

284
00:14:19,450 --> 00:14:22,080
automatic weapons possession, discharge,

285
00:14:22,470 --> 00:14:24,350
are not open to interpretation.

286
00:14:25,160 --> 00:14:28,240
No judge's personal bent is going to help us here.

287
00:14:28,460 --> 00:14:30,420
If Rhoades knows about it,

288
00:14:30,670 --> 00:14:32,690
then one of the cops is already talking,

289
00:14:32,690 --> 00:14:35,680
because Danzig doesn't know how we did what we did.

290
00:14:36,380 --> 00:14:38,090
And they haven't picked him up anyway.

291
00:14:40,140 --> 00:14:40,940
Orrin...

292
00:14:42,220 --> 00:14:43,670
you should leave for this part.

293
00:14:44,230 --> 00:14:47,310
Thanks for your counsel, as always. Invaluable.

294
00:14:48,440 --> 00:14:49,930
I serve at your pleasure.

295
00:14:59,390 --> 00:15:00,340
How?

296
00:15:02,610 --> 00:15:03,670
Wendy Rhoades.

297
00:15:07,880 --> 00:15:09,060
I had a session.

298
00:15:10,950 --> 00:15:12,260
Careless, I know.

299
00:15:14,180 --> 00:15:16,980
You needed connection. Few of us don't.

300
00:15:18,310 --> 00:15:20,250
Should I prepare the materials for her?

301
00:15:20,760 --> 00:15:21,650
Yes.

302
00:15:23,100 --> 00:15:26,960
It would be best if you continue on with her as is,

303
00:15:27,210 --> 00:15:28,650
so we can monitor her.

304
00:15:29,680 --> 00:15:30,600
You're right.

305
00:15:40,810 --> 00:15:41,730
Kids ate.

306
00:15:42,200 --> 00:15:43,290
I waited for you.

307
00:15:47,920 --> 00:15:48,800
Come here.

308
00:16:13,700 --> 00:16:16,550
You were right about Wendy Rhoades.

309
00:16:17,760 --> 00:16:19,070
I told her something compromising,

310
00:16:19,070 --> 00:16:20,650
and it's coming back on me.

311
00:16:21,000 --> 00:16:23,760
Fucking knew it. I told you. I knew it.

312
00:16:24,060 --> 00:16:26,940
She needs to be shut down. Tight. Right fucking now.

313
00:16:26,940 --> 00:16:29,500
Yeah, when the time is right.

314
00:16:31,210 --> 00:16:32,220
But for now...

315
00:16:33,010 --> 00:16:35,430
remember the contingency plan we discussed?

316
00:16:37,220 --> 00:16:38,820
It's time to put it in motion.

317
00:16:40,780 --> 00:16:41,650
Fuck.

318
00:16:44,130 --> 00:16:45,300
It's really happening.

319
00:16:47,020 --> 00:16:47,900
Yes.

320
00:16:51,770 --> 00:16:53,080
How are you gonna play it?

321
00:16:53,210 --> 00:16:54,520
Like nothing's wrong.

322
00:17:02,450 --> 00:17:04,480
So when we tie Axelrod to bribery

323
00:17:04,480 --> 00:17:06,580
of law enforcement officers and obstruction of justice --

324
00:17:06,580 --> 00:17:08,910
we are sitting pretty in Schaefer City.

325
00:17:10,370 --> 00:17:11,930
This is Axelrod in jail.

326
00:17:12,570 --> 00:17:14,300
Real jail time, too.

327
00:17:14,640 --> 00:17:17,140
This is criminal behavior that, if proven,

328
00:17:17,710 --> 00:17:19,660
takes away any middle ground between right and wrong

329
00:17:19,660 --> 00:17:21,640
and marks him wrong forever.

330
00:17:21,640 --> 00:17:22,560
It does.

331
00:17:23,170 --> 00:17:26,180
I am frankly astonished. This is excellent work.

332
00:17:27,000 --> 00:17:28,690
I never should've detailed you over to Eastern.

333
00:17:28,690 --> 00:17:30,640
How did we let him go, Bryan?

334
00:17:31,080 --> 00:17:32,400
I-I don't actually know.

335
00:17:32,410 --> 00:17:34,130
How the hell did it happen, Chuck?

336
00:17:35,360 --> 00:17:38,410
This kind of go-get-em attitude...and competence --

337
00:17:38,700 --> 00:17:40,290
We've missed that around here.

338
00:17:42,130 --> 00:17:43,200
Haven't we, Bryan?

339
00:17:44,280 --> 00:17:45,390
I guess so.

340
00:17:47,860 --> 00:17:48,740
Very good, gentlemen.

341
00:17:48,750 --> 00:17:50,040
What are our next steps?

342
00:17:57,580 --> 00:17:58,570
Good morning.

343
00:17:58,990 --> 00:18:00,040
It is.

344
00:18:06,000 --> 00:18:08,200
- So? - "So"?

345
00:18:11,430 --> 00:18:13,110
That's what you have to say to me?

346
00:18:14,830 --> 00:18:15,760
Wait.

347
00:18:17,380 --> 00:18:19,740
I feel like I walked in halfway through the play.

348
00:18:22,590 --> 00:18:24,130
I decided I wasn't gonna say anything,

349
00:18:24,130 --> 00:18:27,050
but now, looking at you,

350
00:18:27,050 --> 00:18:29,790
sitting there, smiling in my face,

351
00:18:30,220 --> 00:18:31,140
fuck it.

352
00:18:33,360 --> 00:18:34,720
You sold me out.

353
00:18:37,060 --> 00:18:37,610
What?

354
00:18:37,610 --> 00:18:39,670
I tell you something compromising,

355
00:18:40,320 --> 00:18:43,120
and the next thing I know, the fucking Feds,

356
00:18:43,550 --> 00:18:44,770
your husband,

357
00:18:45,210 --> 00:18:46,930
is up my ass again.

358
00:18:57,660 --> 00:19:00,510
Just so you know, and...

359
00:19:01,280 --> 00:19:03,420
I wanna be clear as daybreak on this...

360
00:19:05,590 --> 00:19:06,590
If I go...

361
00:19:08,620 --> 00:19:09,710
You go with me.

362
00:19:15,050 --> 00:19:17,740
I have your web traffic on our server here,

363
00:19:17,810 --> 00:19:19,300
and from your laptop.

364
00:19:19,640 --> 00:19:21,680
You got quite a dark side, don't you?

365
00:19:22,310 --> 00:19:23,480
I would imagine this would make

366
00:19:23,480 --> 00:19:26,600
Dr. Wendy Rhoades look very unprofessional.

367
00:19:26,600 --> 00:19:28,940
And, of course, the whole world,

368
00:19:28,940 --> 00:19:32,210
including the office of the US Attorney for the Southern District,

369
00:19:32,210 --> 00:19:33,840
and the Attorney General,

370
00:19:33,840 --> 00:19:35,110
would see it, too.

371
00:19:38,920 --> 00:19:39,800
It's funny.

372
00:19:42,210 --> 00:19:44,040
I never instructed my man to take these

373
00:19:44,040 --> 00:19:46,010
when he set up the baths, but...

374
00:19:46,460 --> 00:19:47,930
I suppose on, uh,

375
00:19:48,210 --> 00:19:51,010
on some deep level, I knew he would.

376
00:19:53,650 --> 00:19:54,660
And you,

377
00:19:54,810 --> 00:19:57,740
being such a master of the subconscious...

378
00:19:58,050 --> 00:19:59,520
or is that mistress?

379
00:20:01,880 --> 00:20:03,820
I suppose you would've known, too.

380
00:20:06,260 --> 00:20:08,990
I didn't sell you out.

381
00:20:09,440 --> 00:20:11,660
Polygraph me, motherfucker.

382
00:20:11,830 --> 00:20:14,150
I tell you about my issues with Danzig,

383
00:20:14,150 --> 00:20:17,410
and then in, ooh, the space of, what, 48 hours,

384
00:20:17,410 --> 00:20:20,090
there's a fucking investigation underway!

385
00:20:31,490 --> 00:20:33,260
Twelve-thousand square feet of living space

386
00:20:33,260 --> 00:20:35,770
and, of course, complete privacy.

387
00:20:36,520 --> 00:20:37,760
It's lovely.

388
00:20:38,830 --> 00:20:41,850
For people in our... situation,

389
00:20:41,880 --> 00:20:43,170
which would you recommend?

390
00:20:43,170 --> 00:20:44,950
Well, you can pick a school based on the villa

391
00:20:44,950 --> 00:20:46,130
or vice versa.

392
00:20:46,130 --> 00:20:48,400
I have a packet of all those options for you.

393
00:20:49,120 --> 00:20:51,050
And the timing can work as we've planned?

394
00:20:51,050 --> 00:20:53,910
Yes. These particular schools are used to

395
00:20:53,910 --> 00:20:55,420
business people's children

396
00:20:55,420 --> 00:20:57,760
coming and going for a variety of reasons.

397
00:20:57,800 --> 00:21:00,010
Will you be enrolling them under their real names?

398
00:21:00,750 --> 00:21:01,870
What?

399
00:21:02,320 --> 00:21:04,600
Some don't. The stigma.

400
00:21:04,630 --> 00:21:07,660
They want their kids to have a clean run at their new lives.

401
00:21:08,500 --> 00:21:10,910
We can provide fresh passports for all of you.

402
00:21:12,710 --> 00:21:13,960
No.

403
00:21:14,540 --> 00:21:16,350
Yes, their real names.

404
00:21:19,750 --> 00:21:21,100
If I may,

405
00:21:21,570 --> 00:21:24,390
I knew I might be doing this for your husband one day,

406
00:21:24,720 --> 00:21:27,590
but his choices aren't always yours.

407
00:21:28,080 --> 00:21:29,640
You and the children,

408
00:21:29,640 --> 00:21:30,970
you don't have to go.

409
00:21:31,770 --> 00:21:33,990
But are you sure you wanna go through with this?

410
00:21:34,460 --> 00:21:36,310
Because you know you can't come back.

411
00:21:39,700 --> 00:21:41,520
We're all going together.

412
00:21:43,780 --> 00:21:45,340
Let's talk about travel.

413
00:21:45,700 --> 00:21:46,920
Yes.

414
00:21:59,910 --> 00:22:01,510
- Oh, hey. -Hey.

415
00:22:02,730 --> 00:22:05,280
I've been thinking about this burger at least twice a week.

416
00:22:07,220 --> 00:22:09,260
Exiled and then returned.

417
00:22:09,520 --> 00:22:10,930
Damned and saved.

418
00:22:11,080 --> 00:22:13,220
I'm just saying I miss the burger, Bryan.

419
00:22:14,670 --> 00:22:16,960
It's what you're not saying that has my attention.

420
00:22:18,460 --> 00:22:19,720
What the fuck?

421
00:22:21,130 --> 00:22:22,420
Dude.

422
00:22:23,480 --> 00:22:24,710
Are you okay?

423
00:22:24,800 --> 00:22:26,980
Uh, I'm kind of...

424
00:22:26,980 --> 00:22:28,700
fucked up, honestly.

425
00:22:29,710 --> 00:22:31,040
That makes sense.

426
00:22:31,550 --> 00:22:35,750
Here's what makes sense. You didn't...stumble upon

427
00:22:35,750 --> 00:22:37,450
this Danzig-Axelrod thing.

428
00:22:37,450 --> 00:22:38,640
Someone fed it to you.

429
00:22:40,790 --> 00:22:44,680
I've developed sources. One came through. Yes.

430
00:22:44,680 --> 00:22:46,580
One just happened to come through

431
00:22:46,620 --> 00:22:49,650
the minute you walk back in the door?

432
00:22:50,930 --> 00:22:54,210
At exactly the right time for you

433
00:22:54,210 --> 00:22:56,180
to pull that out for Chuck and the rest of the squad, huh?

434
00:22:56,180 --> 00:22:57,500
Look...

435
00:22:57,970 --> 00:22:59,780
I understand how you're feeling

436
00:22:59,910 --> 00:23:01,800
with everything you've put into this.

437
00:23:02,120 --> 00:23:03,630
But we can work together.

438
00:23:04,200 --> 00:23:05,660
We can share the win.

439
00:23:07,840 --> 00:23:09,650
Chuck's the one who gave it to you.

440
00:23:10,610 --> 00:23:14,850
He got it somehow, and he's using you as his shill.

441
00:23:14,850 --> 00:23:17,610
All right, check yourself, right now,

442
00:23:17,610 --> 00:23:19,210
before you come at me with some bullshit

443
00:23:19,210 --> 00:23:21,570
that wouldn't work on a street corner drug dealer.

444
00:23:21,570 --> 00:23:24,820
You are gonna get hurt here in ways you can't see,

445
00:23:24,980 --> 00:23:26,790
and I'm trying to stop it from happening,

446
00:23:26,920 --> 00:23:30,080
for all of our sakes, but you gotta give me the real.

447
00:23:32,890 --> 00:23:35,790
Beneficent as hell, but I'll pass.

448
00:23:36,460 --> 00:23:39,710
Look, I know you bootstrapped your way to where you are.

449
00:23:39,740 --> 00:23:41,490
But I want you to take one look into my eyes

450
00:23:41,490 --> 00:23:44,640
and tell me if you really think that I had it any easier.

451
00:23:48,590 --> 00:23:51,150
If you have an issue with Chuck, take it up with him.

452
00:23:51,160 --> 00:23:54,150
Otherwise, don't piss on my integrity.

453
00:23:55,760 --> 00:23:59,080
Excuse me. I'm gonna go back to eating my burger.

454
00:24:03,950 --> 00:24:06,340
Breaching a country's Air Defense Identification Zone

455
00:24:06,350 --> 00:24:09,240
in Europe today, very tough.

456
00:24:09,240 --> 00:24:10,520
Dangerous for everyone involved.

457
00:24:10,530 --> 00:24:12,310
Which is why I'll pay you double.

458
00:24:12,790 --> 00:24:14,830
Come on, guys, are we solving this,

459
00:24:14,830 --> 00:24:16,490
or am I gonna find someone else who can?

460
00:24:20,510 --> 00:24:21,920
All right, then.

461
00:24:33,160 --> 00:24:35,180
Hi. Where are the kids?

462
00:24:36,070 --> 00:24:38,500
I sent them to Nancy's so we could do this.

463
00:24:40,660 --> 00:24:41,970
"This"?

464
00:24:49,020 --> 00:24:50,700
I know what you did.

465
00:24:54,090 --> 00:24:55,500
I don't believe this.

466
00:24:56,110 --> 00:25:00,380
Everything I've done, no matter what, is for us.

467
00:25:00,380 --> 00:25:03,130
I don't believe that, not anymore.

468
00:25:03,130 --> 00:25:04,960
Not after you broke into my computer,

469
00:25:05,520 --> 00:25:08,110
opened my files, and read my session notes.

470
00:25:08,110 --> 00:25:10,000
You stole the evidence you needed.

471
00:25:10,000 --> 00:25:11,900
I had no choice.

472
00:25:13,390 --> 00:25:15,350
We all have choices.

473
00:25:15,350 --> 00:25:16,820
That's right.

474
00:25:16,880 --> 00:25:19,160
That's right, and I'd do it again.

475
00:25:20,890 --> 00:25:22,300
Because even if you can't put together

476
00:25:22,310 --> 00:25:24,030
what he's done to us, I can.

477
00:25:24,030 --> 00:25:25,910
And that gives you the right to break into my computer?

478
00:25:25,910 --> 00:25:27,090
If you give someone your password, is it really

479
00:25:27,090 --> 00:25:28,060
- ...breaking in? - Yes, it is.

480
00:25:28,060 --> 00:25:30,570
Do not come at me with another word of lawyer bullshit.

481
00:25:30,570 --> 00:25:33,040
You can talk yourself into any kind of justification.

482
00:25:33,040 --> 00:25:35,760
Sure. Yeah.

483
00:25:35,760 --> 00:25:37,610
But, you know, it's no worse than you and your,

484
00:25:37,610 --> 00:25:40,260
"I'm there for my patients" bullshit,

485
00:25:40,270 --> 00:25:43,040
because these patients that you see are criminals.

486
00:25:43,040 --> 00:25:44,490
That's the point.

487
00:25:47,000 --> 00:25:49,830
And all the proof I could ever need is in that computer.

488
00:25:49,830 --> 00:25:51,770
In my own house.

489
00:25:51,770 --> 00:25:53,910
I know this much about the law --

490
00:25:54,010 --> 00:25:56,130
You can't use what you found there.

491
00:25:56,130 --> 00:25:58,140
It's privileged and inadmissible.

492
00:25:58,140 --> 00:25:59,610
And if you do and you're caught,

493
00:25:59,610 --> 00:26:01,350
I won't lie on the witness stand.

494
00:26:01,350 --> 00:26:03,400
Don't worry. A wife can't be compelled to testify

495
00:26:03,400 --> 00:26:04,230
against her husband.

496
00:26:04,230 --> 00:26:06,550
Oh, I won't have to be compelled. I will volunteer.

497
00:26:10,130 --> 00:26:13,840
Jesus Christ, you really are one of them now, aren't you?

498
00:26:13,840 --> 00:26:14,970
Holy shit.

499
00:26:14,970 --> 00:26:16,860
Are you really turning this on me?

500
00:26:16,870 --> 00:26:18,750
You betrayed my trust.

501
00:26:18,750 --> 00:26:21,030
After you were out all night.

502
00:26:21,030 --> 00:26:22,940
And don't give me this crap

503
00:26:22,940 --> 00:26:24,440
about how it was all business either,

504
00:26:24,440 --> 00:26:26,140
because I saw the two of you out there.

505
00:26:26,770 --> 00:26:28,210
Cozy as a couple of teenagers

506
00:26:28,210 --> 00:26:30,610
sharing a cigarette after a backseat fuck.

507
00:26:30,610 --> 00:26:33,460
Wow. You spied on me, too?

508
00:26:35,110 --> 00:26:37,300
No. I wasn't there to spy.

509
00:26:37,400 --> 00:26:39,290
Uh, it was to talk to you.

510
00:26:40,200 --> 00:26:42,130
'Cause I'm desperate, Wendy.

511
00:26:43,930 --> 00:26:45,450
I wasn't up there because of the case.

512
00:26:45,450 --> 00:26:46,860
It was personal.

513
00:26:48,100 --> 00:26:50,280
This man, this motherfucker,

514
00:26:50,280 --> 00:26:52,700
is destroying our lives.

515
00:26:53,580 --> 00:26:55,070
He's driving us apart,

516
00:26:56,530 --> 00:26:57,760
and he's doing it deliberately.

517
00:26:57,770 --> 00:26:58,980
No.

518
00:26:59,610 --> 00:27:02,710
You are. He is an outside factor.

519
00:27:02,710 --> 00:27:05,410
This problem is here.

520
00:27:05,960 --> 00:27:08,110
You could've walked away from this a million times.

521
00:27:08,110 --> 00:27:09,960
- You told me you had. - I can't.

522
00:27:09,970 --> 00:27:12,090
It's not that simple.

523
00:27:12,360 --> 00:27:14,810
Even this, uh, the reason we're here right now

524
00:27:14,810 --> 00:27:16,350
having this conversation,

525
00:27:16,520 --> 00:27:18,910
he knew that I was acting on the bribery

526
00:27:18,910 --> 00:27:20,560
before anyone could've known it.

527
00:27:20,560 --> 00:27:23,220
He will not let me just walk away.

528
00:27:24,640 --> 00:27:27,650
He will not stop until he ruins me.

529
00:27:27,650 --> 00:27:29,480
Now you sound like a crazy person.

530
00:27:29,530 --> 00:27:31,780
He had me followed, all right?

531
00:27:33,100 --> 00:27:35,480
'Cause he's trying to trip me up, he's trying to trap me.

532
00:27:35,480 --> 00:27:38,510
So I had to play dirty right back at him.

533
00:27:38,630 --> 00:27:40,420
Followed? Where?

534
00:27:40,750 --> 00:27:42,090
Trapped you how?

535
00:27:55,530 --> 00:27:57,040
After I saw you and Axe together,

536
00:27:57,050 --> 00:27:59,440
I got very worked up,

537
00:28:00,200 --> 00:28:02,130
past the point of, uh...

538
00:28:05,210 --> 00:28:06,660
I went to see Troy.

539
00:28:10,780 --> 00:28:15,240
And like I said, he had someone on me and, uh...

540
00:28:15,240 --> 00:28:17,110
well, if I didn't get lucky, there would be pictures

541
00:28:17,110 --> 00:28:20,100
on the front page of today's Post.

542
00:28:23,300 --> 00:28:26,100
You went to see her without fucking telling me.

543
00:28:26,100 --> 00:28:27,410
Nothing happened.

544
00:28:29,680 --> 00:28:32,800
And I couldn't go through with anything anyway because, uh...

545
00:28:34,160 --> 00:28:35,750
Because you weren't there.

546
00:28:35,750 --> 00:28:37,060
How touching.

547
00:28:38,420 --> 00:28:39,900
I'm cut off.

548
00:28:40,680 --> 00:28:44,270
I'm cut off from you, from us.

549
00:28:45,660 --> 00:28:48,500
And you sit there and you try to claim moral high ground.

550
00:28:48,500 --> 00:28:50,220
Oh, oh, oh, oh. I claim it?

551
00:28:50,230 --> 00:28:51,730
While you go on working at a criminal organization,

552
00:28:51,730 --> 00:28:55,840
and you can't even fucking admit it to yourself, Wendy.

553
00:28:58,080 --> 00:28:59,560
And you prop it up

554
00:28:59,970 --> 00:29:02,820
and you suck in all that it gives you --

555
00:29:03,020 --> 00:29:05,870
status, money, control.

556
00:29:05,870 --> 00:29:07,180
You know what? It gives me a hell of a lot more

557
00:29:07,180 --> 00:29:09,810
than you do, including honesty!

558
00:29:11,220 --> 00:29:12,580
Really?

559
00:29:14,470 --> 00:29:16,290
What? Like this?

560
00:29:18,150 --> 00:29:19,040
How'd you earn...

561
00:29:19,040 --> 00:29:20,200
...that new hunk of metal that's parked outside?

562
00:29:20,200 --> 00:29:21,730
What's that worth? A quarter mil?

563
00:29:21,730 --> 00:29:23,770
I don't know. I didn't have it appraised.

564
00:29:24,390 --> 00:29:25,450
You know, what you should be appraising

565
00:29:25,450 --> 00:29:26,980
is your conscience.

566
00:29:28,220 --> 00:29:30,350
'Cause you can lie to me about how it makes you feel,

567
00:29:30,350 --> 00:29:32,240
but you can't lie to yourself.

568
00:29:36,770 --> 00:29:38,370
And if you're right there in the middle of it

569
00:29:38,370 --> 00:29:40,430
with a bunch of criminals,

570
00:29:40,430 --> 00:29:42,690
what do you think that makes you?

571
00:29:48,830 --> 00:29:50,750
You don't get to ask me that question anymore.

572
00:29:50,750 --> 00:29:53,060
I am going to take a walk. Pack your shit.

573
00:29:53,850 --> 00:29:55,310
When I get back,

574
00:29:56,120 --> 00:29:57,610
be gone.

575
00:30:58,120 --> 00:30:59,520
Good news, boss.

576
00:30:59,520 --> 00:31:02,170
Uh, banking authorities in Vanuatu have revealed

577
00:31:02,170 --> 00:31:04,720
that our cops have significant holdings there.

578
00:31:04,720 --> 00:31:05,890
It's gonna take some time

579
00:31:05,890 --> 00:31:07,650
these fuckers are not cooperative

580
00:31:07,650 --> 00:31:09,230
before we find that source of the funds,

581
00:31:09,230 --> 00:31:11,450
but we know what we're going to find.

582
00:31:11,730 --> 00:31:13,320
Case is terminated.

583
00:31:22,540 --> 00:31:24,480
What the fuck is going on?

584
00:31:29,070 --> 00:31:31,560
Looked like a winner, but it's not.

585
00:31:33,520 --> 00:31:35,120
'Cause there is no gun.

586
00:31:35,540 --> 00:31:37,270
Uh, there will never be a gun.

587
00:31:40,580 --> 00:31:43,280
That's good legwork, Lonnie. Thank you.

588
00:31:43,280 --> 00:31:45,700
But I don't want you burning out your legs

589
00:31:45,700 --> 00:31:47,570
chasing another ghost.

590
00:31:53,070 --> 00:31:54,650
Bryan...

591
00:31:59,870 --> 00:32:01,090
Okay.

592
00:32:03,930 --> 00:32:05,610
It's Chinatown, Jake.

593
00:32:38,780 --> 00:32:40,330
Been here a while?

594
00:32:40,660 --> 00:32:41,930
Yes.

595
00:32:45,300 --> 00:32:48,670
I didn't expect you back so soon after how you left.

596
00:32:52,630 --> 00:32:54,360
I don't believe that, not anymore,

597
00:32:54,360 --> 00:32:58,130
not after you broke into my computer, opened my files,

598
00:32:58,140 --> 00:33:00,280
- read my session notes...   - Jesus.

599
00:33:00,290 --> 00:33:01,540
You stole the evidence you needed.

600
00:33:01,540 --> 00:33:02,750
I had no choice.

601
00:33:07,900 --> 00:33:09,020
'Cause you can lie to me

602
00:33:09,020 --> 00:33:11,960
about how it makes you feel, but you can't lie to yourself.

603
00:33:12,010 --> 00:33:13,620
And if you're right there in the middle of it,

604
00:33:13,620 --> 00:33:15,370
with a bunch of criminals,

605
00:33:15,370 --> 00:33:17,630
what do you think that makes you?

606
00:33:19,630 --> 00:33:22,210
That's a hell of a question to have to answer.

607
00:33:23,850 --> 00:33:25,040
I know.

608
00:33:31,200 --> 00:33:33,780
I am so sorry to have doubted you.

609
00:33:34,100 --> 00:33:35,810
This is the part where you tell me you're gonna destroy

610
00:33:35,810 --> 00:33:37,340
everything you showed me, right?

611
00:33:37,340 --> 00:33:39,710
I will destroy all copies of it,

612
00:33:39,710 --> 00:33:41,600
whether you believe me or not.

613
00:33:42,080 --> 00:33:43,800
What else are you prepared to do?

614
00:33:47,940 --> 00:33:49,220
Your bonus.

615
00:33:49,660 --> 00:33:51,590
I was planning to give you two million.

616
00:33:52,040 --> 00:33:53,560
It just went up to five.

617
00:33:54,190 --> 00:33:55,710
How do I know you mean it,

618
00:33:56,340 --> 00:33:57,660
that I won't walk down to my office

619
00:33:57,660 --> 00:33:58,820
and find it's one million

620
00:33:58,820 --> 00:34:00,850
and another four you're keeping invested here for me?

621
00:34:00,850 --> 00:34:03,400
I'll wire it to you now, to your own account.

622
00:34:07,740 --> 00:34:10,170
Wags, five sticks wired now

623
00:34:10,170 --> 00:34:11,820
to Wendy Rhoades' personal account.

624
00:34:11,830 --> 00:34:13,680
Whoa! Powerball winner.

625
00:34:16,900 --> 00:34:18,110
Check your e-mail in two minutes.

626
00:34:18,120 --> 00:34:19,360
I will.

627
00:34:20,140 --> 00:34:21,800
I'll triple it for that recording

628
00:34:21,800 --> 00:34:23,260
you played me just now.

629
00:34:25,350 --> 00:34:27,250
It's worth that much to you?

630
00:34:27,250 --> 00:34:29,780
Consider that my opening offer.

631
00:34:33,340 --> 00:34:35,570
He's still the father of my kids.

632
00:34:39,990 --> 00:34:41,190
I had to try.

633
00:34:48,330 --> 00:34:53,080
I quit, Bobby. Chuck was right about one thing.

634
00:34:53,090 --> 00:34:54,810
I can't be in denial about

635
00:34:55,140 --> 00:34:59,110
what this place is, what you are, any longer.

636
00:34:59,160 --> 00:35:01,370
Not after what you showed me.

637
00:35:02,830 --> 00:35:05,490
I know you trade on inside information

638
00:35:05,490 --> 00:35:07,590
and by other illegal means.

639
00:35:08,740 --> 00:35:10,810
Or you let it be done for you.

640
00:35:11,010 --> 00:35:12,240
You encourage it.

641
00:35:12,240 --> 00:35:13,500
Are you taping me now?

642
00:35:14,140 --> 00:35:15,270
No.

643
00:35:15,840 --> 00:35:17,910
I just need to hear myself say it.

644
00:35:18,310 --> 00:35:20,010
Look, I can explain...

645
00:35:20,010 --> 00:35:21,350
Good luck with that

646
00:35:22,400 --> 00:35:23,820
and with everything.

647
00:35:25,070 --> 00:35:26,320
Goodbye.

648
00:36:43,270 --> 00:36:44,500
Yeah?

649
00:37:06,730 --> 00:37:08,070
Where's Connerty?

650
00:37:08,220 --> 00:37:09,890
I don't know. He left.

651
00:37:12,280 --> 00:37:14,270
I know you're pissed.

652
00:37:14,740 --> 00:37:18,040
I get it. But let's channel that, shall we?

653
00:37:18,960 --> 00:37:22,550
How did you know that Tara Mohr was leaking information?

654
00:37:22,620 --> 00:37:24,050
She just felt wrong.

655
00:37:24,330 --> 00:37:27,540
She was always just around, hovering. Why?

656
00:37:27,540 --> 00:37:29,450
She can't be the only one.

657
00:37:34,910 --> 00:37:36,290
We're gonna need personnel files for this floor,

658
00:37:36,290 --> 00:37:39,350
and banking records.

659
00:37:39,360 --> 00:37:41,290
I wanna know who else is wrong.

660
00:37:41,820 --> 00:37:43,050
Yeah, you got it.

661
00:38:06,440 --> 00:38:08,010
Hey.

662
00:38:08,480 --> 00:38:09,910
Everything's set.

663
00:38:10,180 --> 00:38:12,950
All we have to do is... get it to the plane with us.

664
00:38:12,950 --> 00:38:14,570
You're amazing. Thank you.

665
00:38:15,120 --> 00:38:16,830
But we don't have to go.

666
00:38:18,390 --> 00:38:19,630
No?

667
00:38:21,560 --> 00:38:23,240
The leak was Wendy,

668
00:38:24,270 --> 00:38:25,770
but not how we thought.

669
00:38:25,960 --> 00:38:27,790
She didn't sell me out.

670
00:38:28,080 --> 00:38:31,530
Still, case is done.

671
00:38:31,860 --> 00:38:34,620
Rhoades can't act on what he has.

672
00:38:34,640 --> 00:38:35,930
Oh, fuck.

673
00:38:36,790 --> 00:38:38,730
We really don't have to go.

674
00:38:38,750 --> 00:38:40,170
No.

675
00:38:45,870 --> 00:38:48,340
I am so goddamn glad we don't have to turn our boys

676
00:38:48,340 --> 00:38:49,930
into fondue eaters.

677
00:38:52,200 --> 00:38:53,470
And Wendy?

678
00:38:53,620 --> 00:38:54,930
Gone.

679
00:38:56,240 --> 00:38:58,530
For good, I think.

680
00:39:04,460 --> 00:39:06,490
Well, it's for the best, you know.

681
00:39:06,490 --> 00:39:09,330
She outlived her utility as a weather vane

682
00:39:09,330 --> 00:39:11,530
of what her husband was gonna do.

683
00:39:13,280 --> 00:39:14,910
She's more than that, Lar.

684
00:39:16,680 --> 00:39:18,900
You know, I don't really want to talk about her anymore.

685
00:39:22,300 --> 00:39:23,590
Look at this.

686
00:39:23,800 --> 00:39:25,560
There was a time when this was more than

687
00:39:25,560 --> 00:39:29,200
we ever could've imagined having, you know?

688
00:39:30,190 --> 00:39:34,280
We'd always talk about doing without, living simple.

689
00:39:34,280 --> 00:39:36,090
Hard to think about going back.

690
00:39:36,530 --> 00:39:37,770
Yeah.

691
00:39:37,990 --> 00:39:39,460
Really is.

692
00:39:42,250 --> 00:39:44,630
Well, I'll return it all to the bank tomorrow.

693
00:39:46,220 --> 00:39:48,150
You know what? Don't.

694
00:39:48,330 --> 00:39:49,730
Leave it here.

695
00:39:51,710 --> 00:39:53,040
You never know.

696
00:40:06,710 --> 00:40:07,550
That's him.

697
00:40:08,020 --> 00:40:09,150
African-American gentlemen,

698
00:40:09,150 --> 00:40:11,580
Jefferies, Clement. Age 62.

699
00:40:12,070 --> 00:40:15,190
Okay. Let's see if we can Tinker Tailor his ass.

700
00:40:20,060 --> 00:40:21,420
- Dale.  - Sir?

701
00:40:21,490 --> 00:40:23,600
The team needs the latest on our Axe Capital wire.

702
00:40:23,680 --> 00:40:25,640
I need the latest on the wire myself bec--

703
00:40:25,640 --> 00:40:28,320
Don't answer me back. Conveying the intel is your job.

704
00:40:28,320 --> 00:40:29,540
The FBI can't put those wires up

705
00:40:29,540 --> 00:40:31,020
and then not share on the comeback.

706
00:40:31,060 --> 00:40:33,380
Sir, all due respect, I'm awfully confused.

707
00:40:33,380 --> 00:40:35,770
Don't worry, don't worry. We'll straighten it all out.

708
00:40:35,770 --> 00:40:37,280
I'll book a meeting with you and Terri.

709
00:40:54,020 --> 00:40:54,960
What are you eating?

710
00:40:56,420 --> 00:40:57,220
Nothing.

711
00:40:57,450 --> 00:40:59,640
Not here. Too good to pass up.

712
00:40:59,860 --> 00:41:00,860
Bruno, what's hot?

713
00:41:00,890 --> 00:41:02,970
I got a fresh nonna pie and a hot pepperoni.

714
00:41:02,970 --> 00:41:03,790
Nonna pie.

715
00:41:07,250 --> 00:41:07,970
Hey.

716
00:41:09,630 --> 00:41:10,330
Enjoy, eh?

717
00:41:13,260 --> 00:41:14,670
And lock up when youse are done.

718
00:41:15,050 --> 00:41:15,890
Good night, Bruno.

719
00:41:30,590 --> 00:41:31,370
Jesus.

720
00:41:33,650 --> 00:41:35,070
Okay. Now what?

721
00:41:36,900 --> 00:41:39,630
I don't wanna ruin your appetite just as you started digging in,

722
00:41:40,690 --> 00:41:43,340
but... I need to tell you that your boss got

723
00:41:43,520 --> 00:41:46,510
that bogus information on Axe and the cops

724
00:41:47,390 --> 00:41:50,170
by accessing his wife's private notes.

725
00:41:54,410 --> 00:41:55,240
Fuck!

726
00:41:55,450 --> 00:41:56,250
Right.

727
00:41:58,320 --> 00:42:00,290
I'm sure by now he's dropped it.

728
00:42:04,100 --> 00:42:04,950
He has.

729
00:42:05,710 --> 00:42:07,330
Then my part is done for now.

730
00:42:13,170 --> 00:42:15,330
Oh, what the fuck? Come on.

731
00:42:15,330 --> 00:42:16,910
Hang for a minute, Bryan.

732
00:42:18,030 --> 00:42:19,720
Listen to what Bobby has to say.

733
00:42:24,560 --> 00:42:25,590
I can't sit with you.

734
00:42:25,760 --> 00:42:26,620
Sure, you can.

735
00:42:28,440 --> 00:42:29,390
You want to.

736
00:42:31,060 --> 00:42:33,380
Same way you want to stare at the lions at the zoo.

737
00:42:36,640 --> 00:42:37,870
Bach walks around thinking

738
00:42:37,870 --> 00:42:40,030
he's better and smarter than everyone.

739
00:42:40,030 --> 00:42:42,790
- And you know why?  - 'Cause he is.

740
00:42:42,950 --> 00:42:43,730
That's right,

741
00:42:44,130 --> 00:42:46,080
only he says you're just as smart.

742
00:42:48,110 --> 00:42:50,620
Even more focused, younger, hungrier.

743
00:42:51,930 --> 00:42:52,760
Dangerous.

744
00:42:55,350 --> 00:42:56,590
I don't know about any of that.

745
00:42:57,110 --> 00:42:58,350
I know hard work.

746
00:42:58,530 --> 00:43:00,060
Yeah, you work hard.

747
00:43:01,360 --> 00:43:02,950
But it's much more than that.

748
00:43:04,840 --> 00:43:08,360
You're driven the way only someone brought up from nothing,

749
00:43:08,360 --> 00:43:10,320
the way we were, can be.

750
00:43:10,780 --> 00:43:12,860
Chuck Rhoades, for all his ambition,

751
00:43:13,750 --> 00:43:15,650
he can never need it the way we do.

752
00:43:16,230 --> 00:43:18,200
But the guy's had a safety net all his life.

753
00:43:18,200 --> 00:43:20,920
You and me? We never had a fucking net.

754
00:43:23,870 --> 00:43:26,880
That's why it can never work,

755
00:43:27,260 --> 00:43:30,480
in the long-term, you under him...

756
00:43:32,790 --> 00:43:33,750
Because he can't understand

757
00:43:33,750 --> 00:43:35,530
what matters to you the way I can.

758
00:43:40,850 --> 00:43:43,740
I spend every minute of my day

759
00:43:44,340 --> 00:43:45,960
going after guys like you.

760
00:43:46,680 --> 00:43:49,820
That attitude, that focus, that ability --

761
00:43:50,180 --> 00:43:52,720
it's not being fostered where you're at, is it?

762
00:43:53,160 --> 00:43:55,220
It's being thwarted, in fact.

763
00:43:55,970 --> 00:43:56,970
And eventually...

764
00:43:58,360 --> 00:43:59,380
what you're feeling

765
00:43:59,670 --> 00:44:02,240
will turn to disgust and self-hatred,

766
00:44:02,440 --> 00:44:05,160
and in the end, apathy,

767
00:44:06,040 --> 00:44:06,980
if it hasn't already.

768
00:44:06,980 --> 00:44:08,920
Oh, that's your diagnosis?

769
00:44:09,410 --> 00:44:10,570
What's your cure?

770
00:44:11,290 --> 00:44:12,340
You know what it is.

771
00:44:14,350 --> 00:44:17,980
Come work for Bach's firm on my account.

772
00:44:22,390 --> 00:44:23,730
It's a different kind of integrity

773
00:44:23,730 --> 00:44:26,290
where at least you know you're never lying to yourself.

774
00:44:28,530 --> 00:44:30,100
I'm offering challenging work.

775
00:44:30,900 --> 00:44:32,130
You'll be allowed to win --

776
00:44:32,180 --> 00:44:34,670
expected to, on your own terms.

777
00:44:36,140 --> 00:44:38,300
And, of course, you'll be rewarded.

778
00:44:38,960 --> 00:44:40,540
Seven figures, starting.

779
00:44:41,770 --> 00:44:45,220
And an ability to help your family, really help them.

780
00:44:45,710 --> 00:44:49,870
Your mom -- she won't have to work so hard, not at all,

781
00:44:50,000 --> 00:44:51,070
unless she wants to.

782
00:44:53,460 --> 00:44:56,490
Time to take your seat at the grown-ups' table.

783
00:45:01,120 --> 00:45:02,350
That's not who I am.

784
00:45:03,960 --> 00:45:05,130
I can't picture it.

785
00:45:05,140 --> 00:45:07,040
Oh, I think you can picture it now.

786
00:45:09,710 --> 00:45:12,070
The Bryan Connerty at the settlement conference --

787
00:45:12,260 --> 00:45:13,220
he would've stormed out of here

788
00:45:13,220 --> 00:45:14,580
the moment I walked in.

789
00:45:15,870 --> 00:45:16,960
But you stayed,

790
00:45:18,070 --> 00:45:19,140
and you listened.

791
00:45:22,090 --> 00:45:23,150
And like you said...

792
00:45:24,590 --> 00:45:26,630
I stare at the lions at the zoo, too.

793
00:45:28,530 --> 00:45:29,790
Doesn't mean I wanna be one.

794
00:45:30,200 --> 00:45:32,970
Sure, it does. Everyone wants to be a lion.

795
00:45:34,890 --> 00:45:36,850
Most people just never get the chance.

796
00:45:39,140 --> 00:45:40,830
I'm offering you one now.

797
00:45:58,470 --> 00:45:59,870
Thanks for the pizza.

798
00:46:12,820 --> 00:46:13,940
I didn't hear "No."

799
00:46:30,550 --> 00:46:31,240
Yeah?

800
00:46:31,830 --> 00:46:33,940
Source says Rhoades has listening devices

801
00:46:34,010 --> 00:46:35,240
in place at Axe Cap.

802
00:46:35,610 --> 00:46:37,420
Fuck. Fuck!

803
00:46:40,020 --> 00:46:41,460
Okay, get a sweep going now.

804
00:46:41,950 --> 00:46:43,190
Already in progress.

805
00:46:48,490 --> 00:46:49,880
Welcome to the club, sir.

806
00:46:51,270 --> 00:46:53,360
Chuck Rhoades. We spoke earlier.

807
00:46:53,730 --> 00:46:56,340
As I said, I'm sorry, we don't have any suites available

808
00:46:56,340 --> 00:46:57,370
on short notice.

809
00:46:57,620 --> 00:47:00,010
I'll let you know as soon as one opens up.

810
00:47:00,110 --> 00:47:00,960
Thank you.

811
00:47:38,310 --> 00:47:40,730
You've reached Wendy Rhoades. Please leave a message.

812
00:48:14,760 --> 00:48:17,600
All clear again, just like the last two times.

813
00:48:18,330 --> 00:48:19,260
Are you sure you and your guys

814
00:48:19,260 --> 00:48:20,060
were thorough?

815
00:48:21,410 --> 00:48:23,250
You watched. We hit every inch of the place.

816
00:48:25,820 --> 00:48:27,020
So what do we do now?

817
00:48:27,020 --> 00:48:29,600
There's nothing more we can do on this level.

818
00:48:30,870 --> 00:48:31,940
We can only go deeper.

819
00:48:34,720 --> 00:48:35,750
Then go deeper.

820
00:48:37,940 --> 00:48:38,990
All the way down.

821
00:49:26,070 --> 00:49:27,050
Fuck!

822
00:49:46,660 --> 00:49:48,210
There's nowhere left to check.

823
00:49:49,490 --> 00:49:51,030
We've gone down to the rivets.

824
00:49:51,810 --> 00:49:53,470
I say there's nothing here.

825
00:49:54,970 --> 00:49:55,930
Are you sure?

826
00:50:01,870 --> 00:50:03,230
You can never be sure.

827
00:50:36,890 --> 00:50:39,770
I thought your kind could only come in when invited.

828
00:50:41,310 --> 00:50:44,240
Look at what you did to this fucking place.

829
00:50:46,180 --> 00:50:48,950
I wonder what would've made you feel you needed to do this.

830
00:50:50,300 --> 00:50:52,650
But you do know we were never able to get a warrant to bug it.

831
00:50:52,650 --> 00:50:55,140
Oh, not having a warrant wouldn't stop you.

832
00:50:55,150 --> 00:50:58,060
Or maybe there is one buried in the ceiling somewhere.

833
00:50:58,070 --> 00:51:01,710
I can't -- I can't really remember.

834
00:51:02,660 --> 00:51:05,340
What the fuck are you even doing here?

835
00:51:05,380 --> 00:51:06,670
I come bearing gifts.

836
00:51:12,930 --> 00:51:13,750
Open it.

837
00:51:24,040 --> 00:51:25,170
I want you to have that.

838
00:51:27,230 --> 00:51:29,280
- As a reminder.  - I don't need a reminder.

839
00:51:29,540 --> 00:51:31,250
The memory of shoving that up your ass

840
00:51:31,260 --> 00:51:32,850
makes me laugh at least once a day.

841
00:51:32,890 --> 00:51:34,110
Yeah, I bet it does.

842
00:51:37,070 --> 00:51:38,190
But I'm not laughing.

843
00:51:38,190 --> 00:51:39,010
Oh, you should.

844
00:51:39,660 --> 00:51:41,710
The studies say that laughter does more to contribute

845
00:51:41,710 --> 00:51:44,260
to a general sense of well-being than almost anything else.

846
00:51:44,720 --> 00:51:46,400
Oh, yeah. No, of course. I love to laugh.

847
00:51:46,410 --> 00:51:49,260
I'm not laughing now is what I should've said.

848
00:51:49,640 --> 00:51:50,590
Oh, why is that?

849
00:51:51,740 --> 00:51:53,320
Because my wife kicked me out.

850
00:51:54,910 --> 00:51:55,980
Good for her!

851
00:51:58,800 --> 00:52:00,080
But she's not here either,

852
00:52:00,480 --> 00:52:01,800
if you're trying to find her.

853
00:52:04,150 --> 00:52:05,510
We've both lost her.

854
00:52:09,950 --> 00:52:12,030
Well, then maybe you have a sliver of my pain,

855
00:52:13,390 --> 00:52:15,930
because you stripped away everything that matters to me.

856
00:52:16,020 --> 00:52:17,660
You came at me!

857
00:52:17,670 --> 00:52:19,920
Because you're a criminal, Bob.

858
00:52:22,230 --> 00:52:25,650
And it's my job to shut 'em down and put 'em in jail.

859
00:52:25,790 --> 00:52:28,550
Well, if that's true, you're not very good at it.

860
00:52:29,490 --> 00:52:30,870
You're also full of shit.

861
00:52:33,470 --> 00:52:36,540
What have I done wrong? Really?

862
00:52:37,360 --> 00:52:40,790
Except make money, succeed.

863
00:52:43,230 --> 00:52:45,970
All these rules and regulations -- arbitrary,

864
00:52:46,260 --> 00:52:48,740
chalked up by politicians for their own ends.

865
00:52:49,270 --> 00:52:52,170
And these fines you're always going after --

866
00:52:52,800 --> 00:52:54,930
Where do they go? Who gets them?

867
00:52:54,940 --> 00:52:56,150
The poor? No.

868
00:52:56,310 --> 00:52:58,570
The Treasury, the government.

869
00:52:58,700 --> 00:53:01,180
It's taxation by other means.

870
00:53:01,190 --> 00:53:04,790
Save the civics lesson and the Ayn Rand bullshit.

871
00:53:05,890 --> 00:53:08,520
The fines are the minimum of what you should have to pay.

872
00:53:08,520 --> 00:53:10,080
Oh, you decide what cases to take,

873
00:53:10,080 --> 00:53:12,590
and you only take the cases you won't lose.

874
00:53:12,880 --> 00:53:14,580
But you got it wrong with me,

875
00:53:15,260 --> 00:53:16,650
...because this country...

876
00:53:16,660 --> 00:53:19,710
...was built on industry and competition.

877
00:53:19,710 --> 00:53:22,240
So they will always have a place for me.

878
00:53:24,500 --> 00:53:26,580
And maybe a few generations from now,

879
00:53:27,330 --> 00:53:28,990
they'll tell stories about you,

880
00:53:29,870 --> 00:53:31,260
...like they do Jesse James...

881
00:53:31,760 --> 00:53:33,020
....or Billy the Kid.

882
00:53:33,070 --> 00:53:35,870
Oh, the myth is so fuckin' romantic.

883
00:53:36,130 --> 00:53:37,920
The rugged individual who won't back down

884
00:53:37,920 --> 00:53:41,410
to the unimaginative, do-gooder authorities.

885
00:53:42,300 --> 00:53:44,730
Only in reality, those guys stole and hurt

886
00:53:44,730 --> 00:53:46,140
and destroyed lives.

887
00:53:46,140 --> 00:53:49,040
Now you say you don't think you've harmed anyone.

888
00:53:49,270 --> 00:53:51,590
I say that the effect is the same, worse even,

889
00:53:51,590 --> 00:53:54,360
because you infect the entire world.

890
00:53:55,270 --> 00:53:57,520
You throw the whole system off balance,

891
00:53:57,540 --> 00:54:00,440
leaving chaos and poverty in your wake.

892
00:54:01,410 --> 00:54:03,280
I make the system run.

893
00:54:05,100 --> 00:54:08,530
I have contributed hundreds of millions of dollars

894
00:54:08,540 --> 00:54:11,080
in taxes and philanthropy.

895
00:54:14,230 --> 00:54:16,670
I am employ hundreds of people directly,

896
00:54:17,290 --> 00:54:19,680
thousands indirectly.

897
00:54:21,250 --> 00:54:22,170
What do you do?

898
00:54:23,860 --> 00:54:24,760
Nothing...

899
00:54:25,940 --> 00:54:28,430
besides suck from the municipality,

900
00:54:28,500 --> 00:54:30,050
feed off of it.

901
00:54:30,520 --> 00:54:33,970
And in exchange, you what? Keep order?

902
00:54:34,010 --> 00:54:36,920
You're a traffic cop hiding in federal robes.

903
00:54:39,210 --> 00:54:40,390
I'm moved.

904
00:54:41,960 --> 00:54:46,120
I am -- that is gonna play huge to the other guys

905
00:54:46,120 --> 00:54:47,280
...on your cell block.

906
00:54:48,270 --> 00:54:50,150
Oh, you're sure to become President of the, uh,

907
00:54:50,190 --> 00:54:52,790
Libertarian Club of Danbury Federal Prison.

908
00:54:53,410 --> 00:54:55,560
'Cause no matter what you say, that's where you're ending up.

909
00:54:57,100 --> 00:54:58,470
Keep that as a memento.

910
00:54:59,630 --> 00:55:00,820
And every time you look at it,

911
00:55:00,820 --> 00:55:03,460
know that deal is as good as it is ever gonna get for you.

912
00:55:03,460 --> 00:55:05,870
And one day, you are gonna wish like fucking hell

913
00:55:05,920 --> 00:55:07,300
that it was still on the table.

914
00:55:07,760 --> 00:55:10,400
Then you should've kept half of that for yourself, too.

915
00:55:11,980 --> 00:55:14,190
Because when I pull a deal off the table,

916
00:55:15,260 --> 00:55:17,340
I leave Nagasaki behind.

917
00:55:30,490 --> 00:55:32,590
You know the only enemy more dangerous

918
00:55:32,800 --> 00:55:35,330
than a man with unlimited resources...

919
00:55:38,160 --> 00:55:40,060
...is one with nothing to lose.

920
00:55:43,240 --> 00:55:44,900
And that is what you are looking at

921
00:55:45,720 --> 00:55:47,080
right here.

922
00:56:11,910 --> 00:56:19,910
http://app.zimuzu.tv